CHU, FANG-YI

+447477863158

imfangchu@gmail.com

https://fangchu.github.io/works/

I am a UI/UX designer with six years industry experience. My focus is on high quality creativite website and visual design with coding. I am skilled to solve any design problems with user-centred design techniques.

Achievement

· #Struggles - Nominated for best cover design in Taiwan

This book has sold more than 2,000 copies in Taiwan. https://www.books.com.tw/products/0010734823

"The Life of Homeless Dog" - Project published by a Wuo-Wuo Magazine.

Wo Bao Bao is the only magazine in Taiwan that combines design to illustrate issues with animals and raise awareness about endangered species. I cooperated with Wuo-Wuo as a commissioned illustrator and created visuals for the magazine. The magazine is now popular and well-known in Taiwan.

· National College Student Research Scholarship from Ministry of Science and Technology in Taiwan.

I produced and designed an Augumented reality eco-education project. It was experimented at Yong Long Primary School and it received good feedback from the students. The project was later awarded the Scholarship from the Ministry of Education.

Skills

Tools - Sketch, Zeplin, Adobe Creative Suite, Invision, Storyboard, Balsamiq, Paper and Slack.

Programing - Html, Css/Sass, Pug/Jade, Jquery, Javascript, Boostrap, Npm, Gulp, Git and Github.

Work Experience

Freelencer

Web Designer, London August 2019 - Present

- Responsible for visual on the official website and planning the design guideline independently.
- Scoping and production of initial plan from brief.
- Designing engaging and responsive landing pages.
- · Icon design.

Rakuya .Inc (Rental Websites)

UI/UX Designer October 2014 - July 2018



- Set standards for wireframes and user fows, created prototypes for user testing.
- Presented competitor analysis, usability research and design solutions to executive team.
- Redesign and implement the sell/rent objects websites with the team, replacing the old website structure with a new one. This improved user experience on devices and upgraded users' visit rate from 20% to 70%.
- Responsible for UI design of web & mobile apps for website and networking system.
- Extensive experience building responsive websites utilising HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.
- Communicate and collaborate with the development team and marketing team to ensure that designs are delivered as per the brief set.

Grazingcat Design Studio

Web Designer October 2013 - July 2014



- Design the UI, and interaction flow of new web and mobile applications.
- Designed startups' web and mobile apps including strategies, interaction design and visual design. This received high ratings on customer satisfaction survey.
- Responsible for planning and developing e-newsletters and operating facebook media while bringing the most popular articles to the
- Implement different projects with the team. I took part in at least 20 website projects, my roles in Coding (Joomla, HTML/CSS) and Visual Design for websites.
- Knowledge of layouts, graphic fundamentals, typography, print.

ECI.SOFT

Web Designer October 2011 - September 2013

- Collected and organized the requirements from customers for supporting decision.
- Built UI flow and wireframe and prototypes.

Education

Asia University Taiwan (2006 - 2011)

Bachelor of Arts degree in Department of Digital Media Design GPA 82.47 Subjects | Animate and Web design.

Languages

- Mandarin (native)
- English (intermediate)